<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Warsaw Wilanów - Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="monumentsCategory">History</string>
    <string name="natureCategory">Nature</string>
    <string name="otherCategory">Other</string>
    <string name="foodCategory">Food</string>

    <string name="wilanowPalace">Palace at the Wilanow</string>
    <string name="wilanowPalaceDescription">Wilanów Palace or Wilanowski Palace is a royal palace located
        in the Wilanów district, Warsaw. It is one of Poland\'s most important monuments.
        The Palace\'s museum, established in 1805, is a repository of the country\'s royal and artistic heritage.
        The palace and park in Wilanów hosts cultural events and concerts,
        including Summer Royal Concerts in the Rose Garden and the International Summer Early Music Academy.</string>
    <string name="potockiMaus">Potocki Mausoleum</string>
    <string name="potockiMausDescription">An extraordinary piece of funerary art,
        befitting two of Poland\'s most powerful, wealthy and influential families.
        Consisting of a Neo-Gothic canopy with lions holding shields bearing
        the crests of the Potocki and Lubomirski families in each corner,
        on the sarcophagus itself are the figures of the deceased,
        and around the sides symbols of their virtues and interests are displayed.</string>
    <string name="curchOfSantAnne">Church of St. Anne</string>
    <string name="curchOfSantAnneDescription">Located at Wilanów, a church has stood on this exact site since the 14th century.
        The church suffered damage during both world wars and was even used as an internment camp by the Nazis,
        who also looted and damaged it. The church bells dating from 1723 and 1777 survived thanks to the bravery of
        the local people who hid them; today they are housed in the newly built Third Millennium Tower. </string>

    <string name="botanicGarden">Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="botanicGardenDescription">The Botanical Garden was founded in 1974
        is a huge, peacefull park with nice walking paths: roughly half of is taken, according to the map,
        by “useful and ornamental plants”, the second part (arboretum) is “a collection of woody plants”,
        where the azaleas are the most popular among visitors (they bloom in the spring). </string>
    <string name="zawadyBeach">Zawady Beach</string>
    <string name="zawadyBeachDescription">One of Warsaw\'s beaches on the Vistula River: perfect for everyone, families, groups of friends,
        looking to hang out and have a good time. In the old days it would be a summer day destination,
        a typical lazy Sunday activity for Varsovians.</string>
    <string name="morysinNatureReserve">Morysin Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="morysinNatureReserveDescription">Until the beginning of the nineteenth century,
        it cultivated the land, waterbed, agricultural feed and animal farm. Stanisław Kostka Potocki,
        the owner of Wilanów, liquidated the wildlife refuge and managed a wild eye, there was a park here,
        but there are not many traces of the former park. The forest is intersecting paths but it is a wild place,
        there are many dead trees, some are so old that they can hardly be seen from the moss layer.</string>

    <string name="golfClub">Morysin Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="golfClubDescription">If someone is a fan of golf and can not wait for the next game
        or would like to try something new,he can come to the Royal Golf Club Wilanow -
        was founded by players at GPP golf facility on Vogla Street in 2002. Social activities such as picnics
        or Parties play an important role in the life of the club.</string>
    <string name="kuzniaKulturalna">Kuźnia Kulturalna</string>
    <string name="kuzniaDescription">The elegant interior and the neighborhood of the Palace in Wilanów make
        it a great place to go out in the evening, listen to great artists in a cozy atmosphere
        and eat something really delicious at the same time.</string>
    <string name="posterMuseum">Poster Museum</string>
    <string name="posterDescription">The Poster Museum at Wilanów is the world\'s oldest poster museum and
        is part of the National Museum in Warsaw. It was established through a grant of several thousand
        posters belonging to the National Museum, made by the Museum\'s Director, Stanislav Lorentz.
        The Poster Museum opened in June 1968, becoming the world\'s first museum dedicated to this art form.</string>
    <string name="royalWilanow">Royal Wilanów</string>
    <string name="royalDescription">The Royal Wilanów building is something for fans of modern architecture.
        Built in 2015, it has an irregular shape of a glass block, set on a trapezoidal plan with two inner courtyards.
        The facade of the building arches bends, creating a background for the square in front of the building.
        It creates an appropriate background for both historical buildings in the neighborhood and for modern
        apartment buildings in the "Wilanów Village".</string>

    <string name="kuchniaOtwarta">Kuchnia Otwarta</string>
    <string name="kuchniaOtwartaDescription">Kuchnia Otwarta is an everyday restaurant. Fairly fed, seasonally,
        at affordable prices. It is a neighborly place whose aim is strong, friendly relations with the inhabitants
        of Wilanów and the surrounding area. The direction of the cuisine: Polish - according to the author\'s vision of the Chef.</string>
    <string name="stolPolski">Stół Polski</string>
    <string name="stolPolskiDescription">A family restaurant with a Polish modern kitchen, a home-like interior and a large,
        green patio. Loose atmosphere, lots of smile and good food.</string>
    <string name="restauracjaWilanow">Restauracja Wilanów</string>
    <string name="restauracjaWilanowDescription">A restaurant with traditional Polish cuisine and a classic,
        somewhat old-fashioned décor and a peaceful atmosphere. The restaurant specializes in dishes with duck,
        pheasant or deer.</string>
    <string name="plato">Plato</string>
    <string name="platoDescription">Author\'s kitchen of young, passionate people based on European and Asian cuisine.
        The restaurant specializes in seafood and fish. A lot of energy on the plate and in the interior.</string>

    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>

</resources>
